<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Human-centered design specialist, UX Strategist, front-end developer on Hugo Winston Theme</title>
    <link>https://amitux.co.nz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Human-centered design specialist, UX Strategist, front-end developer on Hugo Winston Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:01:03 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amitux.co.nz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://amitux.co.nz/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:01:03 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amitux.co.nz/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description>We know that great ideas can come from anywhere and I&amp;rsquo;m always excited to hear from you. Whether you have a question, any creative idea in mind, or just want to say hello, I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you.
Let&amp;rsquo;s Connect The best way to reach us is via email. I promise to read every message and do our best to respond promptly. Here&amp;rsquo;s where you can drop us a line:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study Capegrace</title>
      <link>https://amitux.co.nz/posts/case-study-capegrace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:39:51 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amitux.co.nz/posts/case-study-capegrace/</guid>
      <description>Project Synopsis During my tenure with the UX Design Institute, I embarked on a project to design a mobile application. This project was inspired by my homeland, New Zealand, a globally renowned travel destination celebrated for its breathtaking landscapes.
This case study will delve into my user experience design process for &amp;ldquo;Cape Grace&amp;rdquo;, a hotel booking app exclusively featuring accommodations in New Zealand.
  Cape Grace Project Synopsis  Identifying the Challenge This research project was born out of the need to address the difficulties users face when booking hotels through websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://amitux.co.nz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amitux.co.nz/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my portfolio! I am a passionate and experienced Senior UX Researcher and Designer, dedicated to creating exceptional user experiences that solve complex problems and drive meaningful impact. With a deep understanding of human behavior and a keen eye for design, I thrive on crafting intuitive and delightful experiences that bridge the gap between users and technology. With a strong background in both research and design, I bring a holistic approach to my work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
